# LUSANDA TSILANA

## JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- **1** 073 378 7046
- ✓ sanda.tsilana@gmail.com
- Cape Town, South Africa
- im View my LinkedIn

## **PROFILE**

I consider myself to be a hard worker. I am always driven to produce good quality work. Due to customer service/call center experience, I am accustomed to working with people and functioning in a fast paced environment. Due to my passion for health and technology, I am currently pursuing a BSc. in Applied Mathematics and Computer Science. I am a **life-long learner** – always willing to try, learn new things and I am able to take feedback.

# SKILLS

- · Web Design and Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Strong Communication
- Sales
- Laboratory Work
- Research

# EDUCATION

### UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH AFRICA

2022 - Current

Bsc. Applied Mathematics and Computer Science

# UNIVERSITY OF WESTERN CAPE

2018 - 2020

BSc. Biotechnology

### HAROLD CRESSY HIGH SCHOOL

2013 - 2017

National Senior Certificate

# EXPERIENCE

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER TRAINEE

CAPE INNOVATION AND TECHNOLOGY INITIATIVE

January 2023 - Present

Programming and Fundamentals:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- Vue JS

#### CLINICAL TRIAL RECRUITER

### SUBJECTWELL

June 2021 - January 2023

Served as a service agent to provide details regarding clinical studies for health benefits. My role included conducting a medical screening to evaluate patient eligibility and transfer pre-qualified patient for further medical screening.

Achievements and Awards include:

- Outstanding Quality Assurance
- · Great Patient Engagement
- Good Time Management Skills
- Team Player

# HOBBIES

- Health
- Technology
- Music

# EXPERIENCE

### **BEAUTY ADVISOR**

**FOSCHINI** 

2018 - 2019

Served as a salesman to make customers aware of the products and promotions available. Played a role in, marketing, sale generation and customer assistance.

- Merchandising
- Replenishment
- Stock Count
- Make-Overs
- Customer Service

# REFERENCES

### Thandi Ndaba-Sher

Manager at Cape Innovation and Technology Initiative 084 806 3374

thandi@capaciti.org.za

### **Nicole Tina Sampson**

Operational Team Lead at Subjectwell 073 247 0876

Nicole.Tina. Sampson@subjectwell.com

### Jayshree Periasawmy

Cosmetics Manager at Foschini 081 534 5757

jayshreep@foschini.co.za